export const questions =  [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'Who is 7th world champion?',
    correct: 'L. Hamilton',
    incorrect: ['F. Massa', 'R.Barichelo', 'K. Raikonnen']
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'What is the team race longer than others?',
    correct: 'Ferrari',
    incorrect: ['Mercedes', 'Alfa Romeo', 'Mclaren']
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Who the champion of 2021 season?',
    correct: 'M. Verstappen',
    incorrect: ['L. Hamilton', 'C. Leclerc', 'F. Alonso']
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What was the engine used in Haas team for 2021 season?',
    correct: 'Ferrari',
    incorrect: ['Mercedes', 'Renault', 'Honda']
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'What team member was M.Schumacher for his first world champion title?',
    correct: 'Benetton',
    incorrect: ['Ferrari', 'Williams', 'Sauber']
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'What driver did end his career for Formula 1 after crash?',
    correct: 'R. Grosjean',
    incorrect: ['K. Raikonnen', 'M. Schumacher', 'F. Massa']
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'What was the track of A. Senna death?',
    correct: 'San-Marino',
    incorrect: ['Monaco', 'Spa', 'Zaandvoort']
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'How many titles of constructor`s cup Mercedes-AMG Petronas Formula One Team has?',
    correct: '8',
    incorrect: ['9', '6', '7']
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'When was the first Formula 1 championship?',
    correct: '1950',
    incorrect: ['1948', '1962', '1952']
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'How many points do pilots earn for the 1st place?',
    correct: '25',
    incorrect: ['10', '16', '20']
  }
];